Finding Aid for University of Michigan News and Information Services Photographs, 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series A circa 1946-1957
  - I-L
    - Jelinek, Jerome (Box A7)
      (see Symphony Orchestra)
    - Johnston, Professor Bruce (Engineering) (Box A7)
    - Joint Judiciary (Box A7)
    - Jones, Nathan, Ann Arbor flutist (Box A7)
    - Journalism Department, 10+ negatives
      - General shots (Box A7)
      - Michigan Interscholastic Press Assoc: High School students (Box A7)
    - Judge Advocate General School (Box A7)
    - Judicature Society, American (Box A7)
      (See American Judiciary Society)
    - Kamrowski, Gerome and wife, Edith Dines (artists: rolling pin art), 5 negatives (Box A7)
    - Kelly, E. Lowell, and wife (Box A7)
    - Kemp, Professor (Box A7)
    - Keniston, Dean Howard (Box A7)
    - Kerlikowske (Box A7)
      (see Buss, Waldo)
    - Kettering, Charles F. (Box A7)
      (see American Alumni Council)
    - Kleinsteuck family, Caroline Kleinsteuck, 2 negatives (Box A7)
    - Koella, Professor (Box A7)
    - Koelz, Dr. Walter N. (Box A7)
    - Kresge Library (Medical Library), 5 negatives (Box A7)
    - Lagler, Karl (Box A7)
      (see Fisheries Research)
    - Laing, Professor Lionel (Box A7)
      (see Pollack, Prof. James K.)
    - Lakes Hydraulic Laboratory, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Landes, Kenneth K. (Box A7)
    - Lane Hall 6 (Box A7)
    - Language Laboratory, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - LaPork, Prof. (Box A7)
    - Latin workshop (Box A7)
    - Laundry, 2 negatives (Box A7)
    - Law Association/Law Institute, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Law Quadrangle/Law School/Law Library, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Lawn, Roger (Box A7)
      (see Students, Expulsion of)
    - League, Michigan, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Lee, Jack K. (Box A7)
    - Legg, Dorothy, receptionist (Box A7)
    - Legatski, Prof. Leo M. (Box A7)
    - Legislators, Michigan, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Library, General-see General Library (Box A7)
    - Life photographer (Box A7)
    - Linguistics Institute, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Little Symphony, see Symphony (Box A7)
    - Little, C.C. former U-M President (Box A7)
    - Lodi House-once U-M Lodi Branch (Box A7)
    - Lydia Mendelssohn Theater, 3 negatives (Box A7)
  - M-O
    - McCartney, Eugene S. (Box A7)
    - McClelland, Marion, secretary (Box A7)
    - McClure, Prof. Thomas F.-art, 2 negatives (Box A7)
    - McClusky, Prof. Howard Y. (Box A7)
    - McCoy, Ernest-Dept. of Physical Education (Box A7)
    - McCullough, Mary A. (Box A7)
    - McDonald, Marian, see News Service (Box A7)
    - McKean, Colonel William B. (Box A7)
    - McKenna, Patricia (Box A7)
    - McLean, Mrs. Statuette of (Box A7)
    - Mailing Room/mail 2 (Box A7)
    - Majestic Theater, razing of (Box A7)
    - Makielski, Professor (plus portrait by) with President Sangren of Western Michigan University, 2 negatives (Box A7)
    - Maps of Michigan 2 (Box A7)
    - Mapping Room (Box A7)
    - Markert, Prof. Clement (Box A7)
      (see Phoenix Project)
    - Martin, Margaret (Box A7)
    - Mason Hall (Box A7)
    - Math Department, 4 negatives (Box A7)
    - Maurer, Professor Wesley H.-journalism, 4 negatives (Box A7)
    - May Festival, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
    - Medical School, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
      (see also Kresge Medical Library; Kresge Research Laboratory; Hospital, University; Polio)
    - Men's Glee Club, 10+ negatives (Box A7)
      (more in box 8)
    - Men's Glee Club, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
      (also in box 7)
    - Men's Physical Education, 2 negatives (Box A8)
    - Messiah Singers-Ruth Orr (Box A8)
    - Metal Processing (Box A8)
    - Michifish, 3 negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan Alumnus-front page (Box A8)
    - Michigan Daily, 6 negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan Day, 5 negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan Federation of Women (Box A8)
    - Michigan High School Forensic Association (Box A8)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (staff, offices & collections), 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan State College (now Michigan State (Box A8)
    - University) Marching Band, 9 negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan Union Opera (Box A8)
    - Michigan Week/Michigan Week Cultural Committee, 6 negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigan Youth Symphony, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Michigras, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Midwest Music Conference, 5 negatives (Box A8)
    - Midwestern Universities Research Association, 5 negatives (Box A8)
    - Miss America, 2 negatives (Box A8)
    - Monuments (Box A8)
      (see Statues, Plaques and monuments)
    - Moore, Professor A.D.-Engineering, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Morrison, Prof. Roger L., 3 negatives (Box A8)
    - Museums Building (includes Anthropology and Paleontology), 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Museums Annex, 3 negatives (Box A8)
    - Museum of Archaeology (Kelsey Museum), 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Museum of Art (Alumni Memorial Hall), 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Music School, include Michigan Singers and Music (Box A8)
    - Education, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
      (see also Band, Marching; Band Symphony; Fipple Flute, Harris Hall, Men's Glee Club; Messiah Singers; Midwest Music Conference; Symphony Orchestra; Union Opera, Women's Glee Club)
    - National Music Camp (Interlochen), 14+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Natural Science Building/School of, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Naval Research, 2 negatives (Box A8)
    - Navy: Naval Reserve on campus; Award to U-M for wartime ed., 3+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Near Eastern Studies 3 (Box A8)
    - Nelson House 2 (Box A8)
    - New York Central-drawing of Burton Tower on menu (Box A8)
    - News Service, U-M, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
    - Niehuss, Dr. Marvin, 2 negatives (Box A8)
    - Noehren, Robert, University Organist (Box A8)
      (see music, school of, March 1952)
    - North Campus, 10+ negatives
      - Aeronautical Engineering/ Wind Tunnel (Box A8)
      - Automotive Engineering (Box A8)
      - General Views (Box A8)
      - Housing (Box A8)
    - North Hall, 6 negatives (Box A8)
    - Novy, Dr. Frederick (Box A8)
    - Nuns, 10+ negatives (Box A8)
      (see Music, School of (1950); also see Students (Brandon))
    - Observatory, University of Michigan, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Odegaard, Dr. Charles E.-Dean of LSA (Box A9)
    - Ogden, Mr. and Mrs., 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Olson, Willard-U-Elementary School, 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Oosterbaan, Bennie-Physical Education, 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Orientation, Student (Box A9)
      (see Registration & Orientation)
    - Ormandy, Eugene-honorary degree (Box A9)
  - P-T
    - Palladium (student publication), 6 negatives (Box A9)
      (see also Women's Physical Education)
    - Palmer Field, 6 negatives (Box A9)
    - Parker House (Box A9)
    - Parking (Box A9)
    - Pharmacy (Box A9)
      (see Chemistry/Pharmacy)
    - Philippines, University of (Box A9)
    - Philosophy Department (Box A9)
    - Phoenix Project (Building; Lab; Fission Products Laboratory, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Photographic Murals, labels for (Box A9)
    - Photographic Services, 3 negatives (Box A9)
    - Photography Club, 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Photography by Students, 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Physical Education (Box A9)
      (see Athletics, Men's Physical Education and Women's Physical Education)
    - Physics, Department of, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Pittsfield School (Box A9)
    - Plaques, commemorative (Box A9)
      (see Statues and Plaques)
    - Plant Department-Buildings & Grounds, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Polio (see also, Hospital, University), 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box A9)
    - Pollack, Prof. James K. (political science), 3 negatives (Box A9)
    - Port Huron High School (Box A9)
    - Potter's Guild (Box A9)
    - Prescott, Kenneth (Box A9)
    - President's house, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - President's office, 9 negatives (Box A9)
    - Prine, Col. (airport manager) (Box A9)
    - Printing Services (Box A9)
      (see North Campus)
    - Psychological Association, American (Box A9)
    - Psychological Services, Bureau of, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Psychology, Department of/Research, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Public Health, School of, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Public Relations Class (Box A9)
    - Publications, Student, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
      (see also Michigan Daily; Palladium; Technic)
    - Queen, Baby campus (Box A9)
    - Quonset Huts (Box A9)
    - Rackham, Horace, School of Graduate Studies (Building: Ann (Box A9)
    - Arbor), 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Rackham Building, Detroit, 2 negatives (Box A9)
    - Railroad Management Seminar, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Raitzin, Mrs. Florencia (Box A9)
    - Randall Laboratory (Box A9)
      (see Physics)
    - Ransom, Mr. Lou, clerical worker (Box A9)
    - Rea, Dean Walter (Dean of Men), 4 negatives (Box A9)
    - Real Estate Clinic, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Regents, University of Michigan, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC), 10+ negatives (Box A9)
      (see also, Judge Advocate Generals School)
    - Retail and Office Clubs of Michigan Conference, 10+ negatives (Box A9)
    - Retail Coal Utilization Institute (Box A9)
    - Rice, Warner (Box A9)
      (see U-M Symbols)
    - Rich, Daniel L. (Box A9)
    - Richard, Hugo, see Students, Expulsion of (Box A9)
    - Rifle Club/Rifle Range (Box A9)
    - Ritter, Professor (visiting, German) (Box A9)
    - Roach, George (Box A9)
    - Romance Languages Building/Dept., 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Rouse, Miss Ruth (Box A10)
    - Rubber Trees/U.S. Rubber Co. (Box A10)
    - Russian Students' Play, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Ruthven, Alexander, Ex-President of U-M, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Saginaw Forest, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Sangren, President of Western Michigan University (Box A10)
      (see Makielski)
    - Sawyer, Dean, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Scheduling Services (Box A10)
    - Scholarships, Bomber (Box A10)
    - Engineering, 2 negatives (Box A10)
      (see also Ford Scholarships)
    - School bus (Box A10)
    - School secretaries, workshop for (Box A10)
    - Scott, Orion, award, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Security Police (Box A10)
      (see University of Michigan Security Police)
    - Service (employee) awards, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Shop Safety (Box A10)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute, 8 negatives (Box A10)
    - Sink, Charles A, books for (Box A10)
    - Small, Marland, of Alumni Luncheon (Box A10)
    - Smith, Shirley W., U-M vice-president, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Smith, Professor (Box A10)
      (see Gallon, Jack)
    - Social Science Library, 3 negatives (Box A10)
    - Social Science Research Center/Project, 3 negatives (Box A10)
    - Social Sciences (Box A10)
    - Social Service Luncheon, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Social Services Institute (Box A10)
    - Social Work, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Michigan Children's Institute (Box A10)
    - School of Social Work (Box A10)
    - Social Work Progress Institute (Box A10)
    - Supervisor's Institute (Box A10)
    - Washtenaw County Bureau of Social Aid) (Box A10)
    - Sociology, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Soo Locks, centennial, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Sororities, listed alphabetically, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - South Quadrangle, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Southwestern Michigan Hospital Council (Box A10)
    - Spanish Festival, 4 negatives (Box A10)
    - Speech Camp, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Speech Clinic, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Speech Department, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
      (see also Drama Season)
    - Stadium/Stadium Communications Center (Press Box), 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Stadium Hills (Box A10)
    - Stanley Quartet, 5 negatives (Box A10)
    - State Fair Exhibit, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Statistics Laboratory, 4 negatives (Box A10)
    - Statues, Plaques and Monuments, 7 negatives (Box A10)
    - Stegath, Mrs. Eugenia (Box A10)
    - Stellfield Collection 10+ (Box A10)
    - Stinchfield Woods (Box A10)
    - Stirton (U-M vice-president) and Harlan Hatcher (Box A10)
    - Stockholders' meeting (simulated) (Box A10)
    - Student Activities/Life and Customs-See also:, 10+ negatives
      - Air Force (Box A10)
      - Athletics Building and class scenes (alphabetically by building and department and college names) (Box A10)
      - Residence halls by name (Box A10)
      - Band, Symphony and Marching (Box A10)
      - Symphony Orchestra (Box A10)
      - Biological Station (Box A10)
      - Camp Davis (Geology) (Box A10)
      - Camp Filibert Roth (Box A10)
      - Commencement (Box A10)
      - Debating Club (Box A10)
      - Drama Season (Box A10)
      - Fraternities (Box A10)
      - Geography Camp (Box A10)
      - Gilbert & Sullivan Society (Box A10)
      - Men's Glee Club (Box A10)
      - Gulantics Hiawatha Club (Box A10)
      - Highway Camp (Box A10)
      - Homecoming Housing (Box A10)
      - Language Lab. (Box A10)
      - Men's Physical Education (Box A10)
      - Michifish (Box A10)
      - Michigan Daily (Box A10)
      - Michigan Union Opera (Box A10)
      - Michigras (Box A10)
      - Michigan Singers (in Music School) (Box A10)
      - Palladium Photography Club (Box A10)
      - Publications, Student (Box A10)
      - ROTC (Box A10)
      - Russian Students' Play (Box A10)
      - Sororities Speech Camp (Box A10)
      - Student-Alumni Speaking Team (Box A10)
      - Student Government (Box A10)
      - Students' Christian Association (Box A10)
      - Tappan Tree? (Box A10)
      - Technic, The Michigan, Staff (Box A10)
      - United States Marines (Box A10)
      - Veterans Readjustment Center, etc. (Box A10)
      - Willow Run Village? (Box A10)
      - Women's Glee Club (Box A10)
      - Women's Physical Education (Box A10)
      - Women's Housing (Box A10)
    - Student Activities Building (Box A10)
    - Student-Alumni Speaking Team (Box A10)
    - Student Government (Box A10)
    - Student Legislature/Building, 4 negatives (Box A10)
    - Student Loan Prints (Box A10)
    - Student, Expulsion of: Freedom meeting (Box A10)
    - Stuligitis, Didi (Box A10)
      (see Athletics: Drum Majors' Contest)
    - Sugar Beet Research (Box A10)
    - Summer Session (Box A10)
    - Survey Research Center (of ISR), 10+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Symbols, University (Seal, Brown Jug, etc.) (Box A10)
      (see University of Michigan Symbols)
    - Symphony Orchestra, 3 negatives (Box A10)
    - Tappan Hall 2 (Box A10)
    - Tappan Tree (Box A10)
    - Tapping, T. Hawley (Box A10)
    - Technic, the Michigan, staff 7 (Box A10)
    - Television Studio, U-M, 10+ negatives (Box A10)
      (see also Extension Service)
    - Temporary classrooms, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Theater (Box A10)
      (see Drama Season)
    - Todd, W.L. (Box A10)
      (see ROTC)
    - Transportation laboratory, 2 negatives (Box A10)
    - Transportation library, 5+ negatives (Box A10)
    - Transportation, buses (Box A10)
      (see Buses)
    - Traverse City students (Box A10)
    - Tucker, Preston (Box A10)
  - U-Z
    - Unadilla Church (Box A11)
    - Union, Michigan, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - Union Opera, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - United States Marines (Box A11)
    - University Hall (Box A11)
    - University High School, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      (see Education, School of and Group Dynamics)
    - University of Michigan Airplane (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan Day, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan Display (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan Employee Activities, 2 negatives (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan New homes at Dexter, 6 negatives (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan Security Police, 6 negatives (Box A11)
    - University of Michigan Symbols, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - University Press/Building, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - University Press Club, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - University Terrace, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - Vaccination, 4 negatives (Box A11)
    - Veteran's Readjustment Center/-Refresher Course/-Village, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      (see also Willow Run Village)
    - Vision Research Laboratory, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - W (Box A11)
    - Wall Street Journal Scholarships (Box A11)
      (see Business Administration, School of)
    - Walter, Dean Erich (Box A11)
    - Warehouse, Fuller Street (Box A11)
    - War Memorial, dedication of, 3 negatives (Box A11)
    - Waterman and Barbour Gymnasiums, 4 negatives (Box A11)
    - Water Tank, Willow Run (Box A11)
      (see Lakes Hydraulic Lab)
    - Ways and Means Committee, State of Michigan House of Representatives (Box A11)
    - Weddige, Emil, 6 negatives (Box A11)
    - Welker, Bertha-clerical worker (Box A11)
    - Wells, Carlton (Box A11)
      (see English Department)
    - Wesleyan Group (Box A11)
    - West Point General and aide (Box A11)
    - West Quadrangle 10+ (Box A11)
    - Whittemore, Prof. H.D., see Grass Lake (Box A11)
    - Wildlife Laboratory, 3 negatives (Box A11)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box A11)
    - Willow Run Hydraulics lab/Research Center, 8 negatives (Box A11)
      (see also Lakes Hydraulic Laboratory?)
    - Willow Run Village, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      (see also Veteran's Village)
    - Wind Tunnel (at Willow Run), 5 negatives (Box A11)
    - Wolverine Girls' State, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - Women's Athletic Building and playing fields, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
    - Women's Glee Club, 10+ negatives
      - Women's Housing (Box A11)
        (See also Housing, Individual residence halls and sororities)
      - General shots, 6 negatives (Box A11)
      - Betsy Barbour House, 3 negatives (Box A11)
      - Adelia Cheever House (Box A11)
      - Martha Cook Building, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      - James Couzens Hall, 7 negatives (Box A11)
      - International Housing (Nelson House, Tappan House), 2 negatives (Box A11)
      - League Houses, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      - Alice Crocker Lloyd Hall, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      - Mosher-Jordon Hall, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      - Helen Newberry Residence, 3 negatives (Box A11)
      - Stockwell Hall, 10+ negatives (Box A11)
      - Victor Vaughan House, 2 negatives (Box A11)
    - Women's Physical Education
      (see also Michifish & Palmer Field)
      - Archery, 6 negatives (Box A12)
      - Badminton, 5 negatives (Box A12)
      - Baseball, 2 negatives (Box A12)
      - Basketball (Box A12)
      - Bowling (Box A12)
      - Children's Classes, 3 negatives (Box A12)
      - Dance/Modern Dance, 10+ negatives (Box A12)
      - Fencing (Box A12)
      - Field Hockey, 4 negatives (Box A12)
      - Golf, 10+ negatives (Box A12)
      - Health, 3 negatives (Box A12)
      - Riding, 3 negatives (Box A12)
      - Swimming, 10+ negatives (Box A12)
      - Tennis, 9 negatives (Box A12)
      - Volleyball, 3 negatives (Box A12)
    - Wood Utilization/Technology Lab, 10+ negatives (Box A12)
    - Workers, Mass of (Box A12)
    - Yost awards (Box A12)
    - Yost Field House 7 (Box A12)
    - Yost, Fielding H. (grave of) (Box A12)
    - Young, Wayne (Pharmacy) (Box A12)
    - Zoology: David L. Nanney (Box A12)
    - Students, individual shots (alphabetical) (Box A12)
    - Non-University Persons (V.I.P.'s, guests, visiting dignitaries, local officials (Box A12)
    - Foreign Visitors (non-university, alphabetically by country) (Box A12)
- Series B 1957-1997 (4" x 5" and 2 1/4" x 2 1/4" Negatives)
  Series B (18.5 linear ft.; ca. 1957-1997) is comprised of black and white 4" x 5" negatives and 2-1/4" x 2-1/4" negatives dating from 1957 to 1997, numerically arranged in rough chronological order. There some color negatives beginning in the late 1980s.The series continues the range of topics covered in Series A.
  - No. 1 to No. 399 January 1957-October 1957 (Box B1)
  - No. 400 to No. 750 October 1957-July 1958 (Box B2)
  - No. 751 to No. 1150 July 1958-June 1959 (Box B3)
  - No. 1151 to No. 1399 June 1959-January 1960 (Box B4)
  - No. 1400 to No. 1799 January 1960-September 1960 (Box B5)
  - No. 1800 to No. 2199 September 1960-June 1961 (Box B6)
  - No. 2200 to No. 255,0 June 1961-May 1962 (Box B7)
  - No. 2551 to No. 2850 May 1962-April 1963 (Box B8)
  - No. 2851 to No. 3099 April 1963-August 1963 (Box B9)
  - No. 3100 to No. 3340 August 1963-April 1964 (Box B10)
  - No. 3341 to No. 3580 April 1964-November 1965 (Box B11)
  - No. 3581 to No. 3870 November 1965-January 1969 (Box B12)
  - No. 3871 to No. 4200 January 1969-October 1972 (Box B13)
  - No. 4201 to No. 4385 February 1973-July 1974 (Box B14)
  - No. 4386 to No. 4565 July 1974-April 1975 (Box B15)
  - No. 4566 to No. 4710 May 1975-May 1976 (Box B16)
  - No. 4711 to No. 4943 June 1976-December 1978 (Box B17)
  - No. 4944 to No. 5198 January 1979-July 1983 (Box B18)
  - No. 5199 to No. 5326 July 1983-December 1984 (Box B19)
  - No. 5315 to No. 5424 January 1985-January 1986 (Box B20)
  - No. 5425 to No. 5575 February 1986-April 1991 (Box B21)
  - No. 5576 to No. 5746 May 1991, 1986-November 1995 (Box B22)
  - No. 5764a to No. 55806 December 1985-July 1997 (Box B23)
- Series C 1961-1997, 35mm negatives
  Series C (96 linear ft.; 1961-1997) consists of primarily black and white 35mm negatives, with occasional color negatives, many with contact sheets. The negatives are a identified by a job number and title and are numerically arranged in chronological order, starting in 1961 and running through 1997.
  There is an index available in the reading room, which provides rudimentary subject access to numbered negatives dated prior to 1973. A searchable database is under construction and may be accessed through the reference staff.
  - No. 1 to No. 144 July 1961-May 1962 (Box C1)
  - No. 145 to No. 300 May 1962-June 1963 (Box C2)
  - No. 301 to No. 400 June 1963-February 1964 (Box C3)
  - No. 401 to No. 547 April 1964-February 1965 (Box C4)
  - No. 548 to No. 635 March 1965-October 1965 (Box C5)
  - No. 636 to No. 735 October 1965-January 1966 (Box C6)
  - No. 736 to No. 865 January 1966-September 1966 (Box C17)
  - No. 868 to No. 977 October 1966-January 1967 (Box C7)
  - No. 978 to No. 1136 February 1967-July 1967 (Box C8)
  - No. 1137 to No. 1227 July 1967-October 1967 (Box C9)
  - No. 1228 to No. 1336 November 1967-February 1968 (Box C10)
  - No. 1337 to No. 1421 March 1968-June 1968 (Box C11)
  - No. 1423 to No. 1517 July 1968-October 1968 (Box C12)
  - No. 1518 to No. 1614 November 1968-February 1969 (Box C13)
  - No. 1616 to No. 1724 February 1969-July 1969 (Box C14)
  - No. 1725 to No. 1824 August 1969-October 1969 (Box C15)
  - No. 1825 to No. 1952 November 1969-March 1970 (Box C16)
  - No. 1953 to No. 2099 April 1970-December 1970 (Box C18)
  - No. 3000 to No. No. 3208 circa October 1970-June 1971 (Box C19)
  - No. 3209 to No. 3396 August 1971-May 1972 (Box C20)
  - No. 3397 to No. 3535 May 1972-October 1972 (Box C21)
  - No. 3536 to No. 3606 November 1972-December 1972 (Box C22)
  - No. 3609 to No. 3758 January 1973-June 1973 (Box C23)
  - No. 3759 to No. 3875 June 1973-October 1973 (Box C24)
  - No. 3877 to No. 4002 October 1973-April 1974 (Box C25)
  - No. 4003 to No. 4102 April 1974-August 1974 (Box C26)
  - No. 4104 to No. 4249 August 1974-February 1975 (Box C27)
  - No. 4250 to No. 4395 March 1975-August 1975 (Box C28)
  - No. 4396 to No. 4540 September 1975-February 1976 (Box C29)
  - No. 4541 to No. 4687 February 1976-June 1976 (Box C30)
  - No. 4688 to No. 4830 June 1976-November 1976 (Box C31)
  - No. 4831 to No. 4944, November 1976-February 1977 (Box C32)
  - No. 4945 to No. 5066 February 1977-July 1977 (Box C33)
  - No. 5067 to No. 5200 July 1977-October 1977 (Box C34)
  - No. 5201 to No. 5309 October 1977-January 1978 (Box C35)
  - No. 5310 to No. 543,0 February 1978-May 1978 (Box C36)